Guide to the Skidmore, Owings & Merrill: Michael McCarthy records, 1970-1998.
Skidmore, Owings & Merrill: Michael McCarthy records
- Series VII. Architectural Projects, Commissions, and Built Works, 1964-1998 (SOM Years)
  - Abu Dhabi National Oil Company - Cairo Ophthalmology Hospital
    - Abu Dhabi Retail Center (H. E. Sheik Nahyan bin Mubarak al-Nahyan), Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates, 1996
      Mixed-use complex to include retail, entertainment, hotel, and residential components. Three schemes were presented to the client.
      - Prospectus with reduced copies of drawings and area calculations, Undated (Box 34)
    - Al-Ahli Bank of Kuwait (K.S.C.) Headquarters Building, Kuwait City, Kuwait, 1979–1988
      SOM Project #2050
      Architecture and interiors for bank headquarters. Three different schemes were proposed. The banking hall is an enclosed cage of polished bronze, crafted in Denmark. For general descriptive material on Kuwait, see Commercial Bank of Kuwait.
      - Working drawings-Plans, Elevations, Tellers counters elevations and sections, Banking Hall Canopy Dome plan and sections (Box 60)
      - Working drawings-Plans, Elevations, Tellers counters elevations and sections, Banking Hall Canopy Dome plan and sections (Box 61a)
      - Working drawings-Plans, Elevations, Tellers counters elevations and sections, Banking Hall Canopy Dome plan and sections (Box 61b)
      - Working drawings-Plans, Elevations, Tellers counters elevations and sections, Banking Hall Canopy Dome plan and sections (Box 61c)
      - Working drawings-Plans, Elevations, Tellers counters elevations and sections, Banking Hall Canopy Dome plan and sections (Box 72)
      - Working drawings, Undated (Mapcase-folder 9)
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 39)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 47)
      - Correspondence, projections, conceptual sketches, presentation outline, Al-Ahli Bank annual report, published articles, Undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Photocopies of photographs (model and exterior)., Undated (Box 34)
    - Alexander & Alexander, Avenue of the Americas, New York, 1976–1978
      The headquarters of this major international insurance brokerage/management consulting firm occupy one floor of the Celanese Building. This was an interior design project, including the selection of nearly one hundred original works of art from around the world.
      - Working drawings/Plans (Box 62)
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 39)
      - Project summary and fact sheet, Undated (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - American Can Company Headquarters, Greenwich, Connecticut, 1969–1973
      This corporate headquarters in a suburban setting is a reinforced concrete structure placed across a ravine so that a terraced podium connects the high ground on each side, from which rises a main office building of three stories with a large central court and a one-story executive building. Service floors and parking are below the podium, resulting in the minimum possible change to the character of the original site. Sasaki, Dawson & DeMay were the landscape architects.
      - Drawings-Copies of perspective and section in McCarthy's interview portfolio, Undated (Box 32)
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 39)
      - Project summary, description, statistics, professional credits, newspaper clippings, and published articles, Undated (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Project fact sheet and description, Undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 47)
    - Baltimore Freeway System, Baltimore, Maryland, 1968
      SOM was chosen as the leader of a four-firm Urban Design Concept Team to investigate and attempt to mitigate the community disruption that occurs as a result of freeway constructions. SOM was specifically responsible for management of urban design, planning, highway aesthetics, and landscaping.
      - Drawings-Copies of perspective and section in McCarthy’s interview portfolio, Undated (Box 32)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 47)
      - Project fact sheet and description, Undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Banque Bruxelles Lambert, Brussels, Belgium, 1965
      1988 - 1993 Addition
      SOM Project #6256
      Originally designed by Gordon Bunshaft of SOM in 1956, the current project included a new wing and link added to the Banque Lambert, creating an H-shaped plan with gardens in newly designed courtyards. The addition includes trading floors, an auditorium, and parking.
      - Working Drawings, Precast details (Box 6a, 6b, 6c, 7, 8, 9, 10, 72)
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 40)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 47)
      - Design program (November 21st, 1956), project summary and fact sheet, awards applications, and published articles, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 19&20)
    - Beijing Capital Jewelry Workshops (Beijing Center), Chang Pu Pearl Street, Beijing, China, 1995
      Designed to have been located against the Red Wall of the Forbidden City in the Wang Fu Jing commercial district, the project included courtyards, shade trees, gardens, and an interior shopping arcade. Not built.
      - Presentation Drawing- Second level Plan, Undated (Box 72)
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 40)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 47)
      - Awards applications, Undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
      - Prospectus including reduced copies of drawings and cost estimates, Undated (Box 34)
    - Cairo Ophthalmology Hospital, Cairo, Egypt, 1996
      Planning, programming, and architecture for a 40-bed health facility including four major eye operating suites, laser rooms, and an ambulatory care center.
      - Slides, Undated (Box 47)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank projects
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Paris, France, 1973
      Renovation
      - Slides, Undated (Box 47)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 410 Park Avenue, New York, 1959
      1976-1978 Renovations
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 40)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 47)
      - Published articles, Undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Headquarters, Facility (Woolgate House), London, England, 1978 - 1981
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Branch Facility, Rosario, Argentina, 1981
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
        Unmarked project photo in folder.
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, ATM Prototype (Chase Convenience Banking), 1980 - 1982
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 40)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Branch Facility, Singapore, 1982
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, (Banco LAR), Belem, Brazil, 1982
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
        Same project photo appears for both Belem and Curitiba sites. Unmarked.
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
      - Size (area) data, Undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, (Banco LAR), Curitiba, Brazil, 1979 - 1983
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Headquarters Facility, 25 de Mayo 140, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1983
      Plaza San Martin site, 1981, unbuilt
      Avenida del Norte site, 1982, unbuilt
      Alteration of nine floors and facade of existing tower.
      - Photographs, 1981, Undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
      - Size (area) data, Undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, (Banco LAR), Branch Facility, Manaus, Brazil, 1981 - 1983
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
      - Size (area) data, Undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Headquarters Facility, Lima, Peru, 1983
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Headquarters Facility, Panama City, Panama, c. 1981 - 1984
      Thirteen-story office building.
      - Working drawings (tracings) (Box 83)
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Photographs (oversized), Undated (Box 33)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
      - Project data sheet, Undated (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Headquarters Facility, Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic
      1983 - 1985 Addition and renovations
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Branch Facility (Chase Soho), Broadway at Houston Street, New York, 1984 - 1985
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Project summary, list of credits, correspondence, published articles, and newspaper clippings, Undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Operations Center, Bournemouth, England, 1984 - 1989
      Schematic design for expansion of operations building; construction of four-story operations building
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
      - Site and design feasibility reports and design specifications, Undated (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Operations Center, Holmdel, New Jersey, 1987 - 1991
      SOM Project #6033 and #6033-005 (interiors)
      Planned expansion of the bank’s office space to suburban New Jersey
      Not constructed
      - Drawings - Contour, topographic, and zoning maps; preliminary site plans; site plans; alternate site plans; surveys; design sketches; Plan Archives One and Two; master plans; sections; preliminary design and approval process working drawings for office and cafeteria interiors., Undated (Mapcase-folder 10-14)
      - Drawings - Contour, topographic, and zoning maps; preliminary site plans; site plans; alternate site plans; surveys; design sketches; Plan Archives One and Two; master plans; sections; preliminary design and approval process working drawings for office and cafeteria interiors. (Box 68, 69, 70, 71a, 71b, 72)
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
      - Project fact sheet, newspaper clippings, and published articles, Undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Technical documents: SOM File index number / Description, Undated
        - 6033 / 100 Project administration (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - 6033 / 110 Publicity and promotion (Box 1, Folder 2)
        - 6033 /130 Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 3)
        - 6033 /133 Meeting minutes (Box 1, Folder 4-7)
        - 6033 /134 Reports: Detention pond analysis (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - 6033 /135 Transmittals (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
        - 6033 /141 Cost estimates (Box 1, Folder 11-15)
        - 6033 /150 Codes, permits, agencies (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - 6033 /160 Pre-construction (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
        - 6033 /162 Planning (acoustics) (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - 6033 /163 Design (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - 6033 /200 Sitework (Box 1, Folder 22-25)
        - 6033 /210 Site Survey (Box 1, Folder 26)
        - 6033 /220 Surface investigation (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - 6033 /240 Subsurface investigation (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - 6033 /720 Waterproofing (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - 6033 /800 Doors, windows, glass (Box 1, Folder 30)
        - 6033 /1110 Food service equipment (Box 1, Folder 31)
        - 6033 /1150 Telecommunications equipment (Box 1, Folder 32)
        - 6033 /1510 Plumbing, fireproofing (Box 1, Folder 33-35)
        - 6033 /1710 Life safety (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Headquarters Facility, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1969
      1989-1991 Renovations
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
      - Project summary and newspaper clippings, Undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Operations Center (Chase Financial Services Center, Metrotech, Brooklyn, New York, 1988-1992
      The major operations center for the bank, Chase Metrotech consists of a two building complex whose large lower floors act as a podium for the slender 23-story tower. The simple geometric forms and the use of such detailing as corbelled brick corners respond sympathetically to the character of the neighboring 19th-century landmarked houses. At the same time, the backlit tower distinguishes the complex on the Brooklyn skyline.
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 10-14)
      - Photographs (oversized), Undated (Box 33)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
      - Project summary, RFPs, studies, and published articles, Undated (Box 25, Folder 30-31)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Operations Center, Kohoku New Town, Yokohama, Japan, 1991-1993
      Master plan and architecture consisting of two office buildings, art gallery, and public spaces.
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 15-16)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
      - Project summary and context location map, Undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Lobby, One Chase Manhattan Plaza, New York
      1973-1997 Continuing services
      1992-1994 Lobby renovation
      - Plans, Elevations, Details, Undated (Box 94a, 94b)
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 40)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 47)
      - Project summary, fact sheets, newspaper clippings, and published articles, Undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Trading Facility, One Chase Manhattan Plaza, New York, 1957-1961
      1992-1994 Renovations
      SOM Project #92140
      Complete renovation of trading operation of the bank.
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 40)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 47)
      - Published articles, Undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Working Drawings: SOM Shop drawing file number / Description, Undated
        - 92140-012 05700-16000, Trading room mockup (Box 5, Folder 31-37)
        - 92140-020 03315-16620, Other drawings and associated information (Box 5, Folder 38-44)
        - Other drawings and associated information (Box 6, Folder 1-25)
        - Other drawings and associated information (Box 7, Folder 1-41)
        - Other drawings and associated information (Box 8, Folder 1-35)
        - Other drawings and associated information (Box 9, Folder 1-39)
        - Plans, Metal ceiling details (Box 72)
        - Partition, Door, Stair, Miscellaneous details, Metal ceiling plan, Column enclosure and connector cover details, Symbols, abbreviations and notes, Plans, Elevations, Toilet plans and elevations, Base building modifications, UPS building and generators, Roofing details, UPS elevation and generators (Box 94a)
        - Metal Ceiling details, Architectural woodwork, Miscellaneous details, Common Center details, Floor elevations and details, Reflected Ceiling Plans, Power and Communication Plan, Floor and roof plans (Box 94b)
      - Technical documents: SOM File index number / Description, Undated
        - 92140/000 Project Summary (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - 92140/016 CAD services (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - 92140/019 Furniture (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - 92140/020 Field memoranda (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - 92140/031 Command Center revisions (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - 92140/032 Data Center revisions (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - 92140/034 14th Floor FX revisions (Box 2, Folder 7)
        - 92140/100 Project administration (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - 92140/101 Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - 92140/102 Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - 92140/102 Transmittal (Box 2, Folder 11)
        - 92140/110 Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 12)
        - 92140/130 Project review booklet, March 03, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        - 92140/131 Planning and preliminary schedules of work (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
        - 92140/132 Construction photographs (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - 92140/133 Meeting minutes (Architect, Contractor, Construction) (Box 2, Folder 17-21)
        - 92140/133 Project review booklet, July 15, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - 92140/134 Project review booklet, August 19, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        - 92140/135 Transmittals: Chase (Box 2, Folder 24-30)
        - 92140/135 Transmittals: Jaros, Baum & Bolles (Consulting Engineers) (Box 3, Folder 1-4)
        - 92140/135 Transmittals: Cantor (Consulting Engineers) (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - 92140/135 Transmittals: Lebowitz/Gould (Design) (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - 92140/135 Transmittals: Cole-Gillman (Consulting Architects) (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - 92140/135 Transmittals: Horton-Lees (Lighting) (Box 3, Folder 8)
        - 92140/135 Transmittals: Shen, Milson & Wilke (Acoustics) (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - 92140/135 Transmittals: Humphreys & Harding (Contractors) (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - 92140/135 Transmittals: Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - 92140/141 Cost estimates (Box 3, Folder 12-15)
        - 92140/150 Codes, permits, inspections (Box 3, Folder 16-18)
        - 92140/154 Codes, permits, inspections (Box 3, Folder 19)
        - 92140/155 Approvals (Box 3, Folder 20)
        - 92140/156 EPA filing requirements (Box 3, Folder 21)
        - 92140/160 Pre-construction, plan of Trading Room (Box 3, Folder 22)
        - 92140/161 Schedule and decisions matrix, environments (Box 3, Folder 23)
        - 92140/162 Checklist of open items and responses (Box 3, Folder 24)
        - 92140/167 Preliminary design guidelines (Box 3, Folder 25)
        - 92140/170 Project review booklet, February 11, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
        - 92140/170 Project review booklet, April 13, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
        - 92140/170 Shop drawing transmittal log, correspondence /171 Bids (Box 3, Folder 28)
        - 92140/171 Bids (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
        - 92140/172 Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 31)
        - 92140/173 Bulletins (Box 3, Folder 32)
        - 92140/174 Project review booklet, May 16, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
        - 92140/174 Project review booklet, June 21, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        - 92140/174 Change order review forms (Box 4, Folder 2)
        - 92140/175 Requests for change orders and responses (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
        - 92140/176 VESDA system (Box 4, Folder 5)
        - 92140/177 Payment requisitions (Box 4, Folder 6-13)
        - 92140/177 Project review booklet, October 14, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 14)
        - 92140/178 Field memoranda (Box 4, Folder 15-19)
        - 92140/179 Discrepancy log/field reports (Box 4, Folder 20-22)
        - 92140/190 Inspections, bid requests (Box 4, Folder 23)
        - 92140/192 Shop drawing submittal log (Box 4, Folder 24)
        - 92140/330 Concrete testing/inspection (Box 4, Folder 25)
        - 92140/510 Preparatory phase structural steel work (Box 4, Folder 26)
        - 92140/530 Lighting, stair construction/inspection (Box 4, Folder 27)
        - 92140/540 Structural steel testing inspection (Box 4, Folder 28)
        - 92140/580 Steel coating system/inspection (Box 5, Folder 1)
        - 92140/610 Doors, filing cabinets (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - 92140/700 Acoustics (Box 5, Folder 3)
        - 92140/720 Waterproofing/sealant/steel penetration details (Box 5, Folder 5)
        - 92140/730 Roofing (Box 5, Folder 4)
        - 92140/740 Fireproofing testing/inspection (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
        - 92140/750 Fire-stopping testing/inspection (Box 5, Folder 8)
        - 92140/800 Doors, windows, glass/sealants (Box 5, Folder 9)
        - 92140/830 Locks (Box 5, Folder 10)
        - 92140/1000 Signage, miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 11)
        - 92140/1100 Food service (Box 5, Folder 12)
        - 92140/1110 Food service (Box 5, Folder 13)
        - 92140/1140 Audiovisual (Box 5, Folder 14)
        - 92140/1150 Lockers, copiers, audiovisual (Box 5, Folder 15)
        - 92140/1200 Miscellaneous equipment (Box 5, Folder 16)
        - 92140/1230 Trading desks (Box 5, Folder 17)
        - 92140/1240 Dealers desks (Box 5, Folder 18)
        - 92140/1332 Meeting minutes (Box 5, Folder 19)
        - 92140/1500 HVAC (Box 5, Folder 20)
        - 92140/1510 Sprinkler system (Box 5, Folder 21)
        - 92140/1600 Electrical, emergency power supply (Box 5, Folder 22-25)
        - 92140/1610 Lighting (Box 5, Folder 26)
        - 92140/1700 Electrical (Box 5, Folder 27)
        - 92140/1710 Life Safety (Box 5, Folder 28)
        - 92140/1730 Security, access control system (Box 5, Folder 29)
        - 92140/1750 Cable (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, Operations Center, Jersey City (Newport), New Jersey
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
  - Chemical Bank - Hospital for Special Surgery projects
    - Chemical Bank, Jericho, New York, 1987
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
    - Chrysler Corporation, Pan Am Building, New York, 1983-1984
      SOM Project #0764
      Space planning, interior design, and furniture design for boardroom facilities and office of the chairman and Chief Executive Officer.
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
      - Project summary and published articles, Undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Citicorp at Court Square, Long Island City, New York, 1987-1989
      Raul de Armas, design partner
      1994-1995, Proposed revisions
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
      - Videotapes of flow visualization: wind tunnel studies: 1) effects with and without tower, 2) effects of canopies and trees, June 28, 1994 (Box 41)
    - Commercial Bank of Kuwait, Ahmad Al-Jaber II Operations Center, Kuwait City, Kuwait, 1979-1984
      SOM Project #2020, #2021, #2035, #2040, and #2050
      Three schemes (A, B, and C) were designed for a new headquarters, but none were built. The client decided instead to construct an operations center.
      - Working drawings (Box 74a, 74b)
      - 021/02200-1600 SOM Shop drawings, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1-30)
      - Photographs, Undated (Box 41, Folder 21-22)
      - Slides, Undated (Box 48)
      - Project summary, design development report, security recommendations, and published articles. General descriptive material on Kuwait, including maps, published articles, and newspaper clippings, Undated (Box 25, Folder 33-34)
      - CBK Annual Report, 1978 (Box 33)
      - Technical documents: SOM File index number / Description
        - 2021 /100 General correspondence, Undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
        - 2021 /102 Procedures, Undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
        - 2021 /130 Job progress, Undated (Box 10, Folder 33)
        - 2021 /135 Transmittals, Undated (Box 10, Folder 34)
        - 2021/[various index numbers] Telexes, Sept. 1983 - July 1984 (Box 10, Folder 35)
        - 2021/[various index numbers] Telexes, Jan - May 1985 (Box 10, Folder 36)
        - 2021/[various index numbers] Telexes, Jan - May 1985 (Box 10, Folder 37)
        - 2021/150 Meeting minutes, Undated (Box 10, Folder 38-39)
        - 2021/172 Owner telexes, Undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
        - 2021/173 Architect telexes, Undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
        - 2021/174 Pace telexes, Undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
        - 2021/175 Shaw & Hatton telexes, Undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
        - 2021/210 Interiors, Undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
        - 2021/230 Architectural, Undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
        - 2021 /250 Mechanical, Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
        - 2021/260 Electrical, Undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
        - 2021/300 General Contractors, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
        - 2021/301 Timetables, progress reports (including progress photographs), Undated (Box 11, Folder 4-9)
        - 2021/301 Progress reports and program of works (oversize), Undated (Box 33)
        - 2021/303 Purchase orders, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
        - 2021/306 Shop drawings transmittals, pace, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11-14)
        - 2021/310 Subcontractors, Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
        - 2021/311 Site, Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
        - 2021/312 Demolition, Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
        - 2021/314 Structural, Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
        - 2021/315 Architectural, Undated (Box 11, Folder 19-28)
        - 2021/315 Architectural, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1-6)
        - 2021/316 Mechanical, fire, water systems, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7-14)
        - 2021/317 Electrical, Undated (Box 12, Folder 15-22)
        - 2021/318 Equipment, wiring diagrams, Undated (Box 12, Folder 23-24)
        - 2021/319 Elevators, Undated (Box 12, Folder 25-26)